My child, these may be the last words I get to leave you
ลูกเอ๋ย นี่อาจเป็นคำสุดท้ายที่แม่จะได้บอกกับลูกแล้ว
I've always thought of the characters in my stories as my children
แม่คิดมาตลอดว่า ตัวละครในเรื่องราวก็เปรียบเสมือนลูก ๆ ของแม่
Loving each one of them just like a mother would
รักพวกเขาทุกคนเหมือนที่แม่คนหนึ่งจะรักลูกของตัวเอง
But you are the most extraordinary of them all
และลูกคือเด็กที่พิเศษที่สุดในบรรดาพวกเขาทั้งหมด
You alone can defy the fate of this world
มีแค่ลูกที่จะท้าทายโชคชะตาของโลกนี้
And write the perfect ending to my story
และเขียนตอนจบที่สมบูรณ์แบบให้กับเรื่องราวของแม่
You alone shall leave these pages...
มีแค่ลูกที่จะออกจากหน้ากระดาษนี้...
For a future I will not see
และมุ่งไปยังอนาคตที่แม่ไม่ได้เห็น
Still, I say to you... Fly, my sweet child
แต่ถึงยังไง แม่ก็จะยังบอกว่า... บินไปเถอะ ลูกรัก
Just like a forest breeze yearns for the open sky
เหมือนกับสายลมในป่า ที่โหยหาท้องนภา
Head into the unknown and seek an adventure to call your own
ออกเดินทางไปยังที่ที่ไม่รู้จัก แล้วตามหาการผจญภัยที่เป็นของตัวเอง
If you meet a dragon bright as a thousand jewels, dance through the air together
ถ้าวันหนึ่งได้พบมังกรที่ส่องประกายดั่งอัญมณีนับพัน ก็จงร่ายรำกับมันในอากาศเถอะ
You are not alone, for this world has accepted your place in it
ลูกไม่ได้อยู่เพียงลำพัง เพราะโลกนี้ได้ยอมรับการมีอยู่ของลูกแล้ว
Do not lose heart. You still have many wishes left to fulfill
อย่าเพิ่งหมดหวังเลย ยังมีความปรารถนาอีกมากมายที่รอให้ทำสำเร็จอยู่
A long tale awaits you, my love
เรื่องราวอันยาวนานกำลังรออยู่นะ ลูกรัก
Let songs and flowers be the ink that fills its pages
ให้เสียงเพลงและดอกไม้ตามเส้นทาง เป็นน้ำหมึกในหน้ากระดาษของลูกนะ
Take my pen and use it to continue your story
รับปากกาของแม่ไป แล้วเขียนเรื่องราวของลูกต่อไปเถอะ